avianweb.com 2016-04-12

# beautyofbirds Site Privacy Policy

**Avianweb LLC** (hereafter referred to as **Avianweb** ) is committed to the privacy of the visitors of this website. The following outlines our privacy policy, and how we treat personally identifiable information collected from our visitors and users.

### What is Covered by our Privacy Policy  ...

  * The way we treat personally identifiable information collected by Avianweb through this website.
  * This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Avianweb does not own nor control, or of persons that Avianweb does not employ or manage, including any third-party content contributors bound by contract and any third-party websites to which the Avianweb links.

### Collection and Use of Personal Information

  * You can visit this website without revealing any personal information. However, if you wish to purchase any products or subscriptions, you may need to go through a simple registration process. 
  * This may require your personal contact information and/or your company contact information. The Avianweb will use this information ONLY to reply to your inquiries, to provide you with requested products and services, and to contact you regarding new products and services.
  * By voluntarily providing us with the requested personal information, you consent to the collection and use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

### Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information

  * Avianweb automatically receives and records non-personal information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address and the page you requested. Avianweb may use this information to customize the advertising and content you see and to fulfill your requests for certain products and services. However, Avianweb does not connect this non-personal data to any personal information collected from you.
  * Avianweb also allows third party companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Again, these cookies are not connected to any personal information. Third party cookie usage is subject to their own privacy policies, and Avianweb assumes no responsibility or liability for this usage.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

  * Avianweb may disclose your personal information to third parties who work on behalf of Avianweb to provide products and services requested by you. We will share personal information for these purposes only with third parties whose privacy policies are consistent with ours or who agree to abide by our policies with respect to personal information
  * Avianweb may otherwise disclose your personal information when: 
    * ... we have your express consent to share the information for a specified purpose;
    * ... we need to respond to subpoenas, court orders or such other legal process;
    * ... we need to protect the personal safety of the users of our websites or defend the rights or property of Avianweb
    * ... we find that your actions on our websites violate the Avianweb Terms of Use document or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services.

### Consent

  * If you do not consent to the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information as outlined in this policy, please do not provide any personal information to Avianweb. If you have provided personal information to Avianweb and no longer consent to its use or disclosure as outlined herein, please notify Avianweb at [[email protected]](http://www.cloudflare.com/email-protection)  

### Security

  * Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be considered 100% secure. We are doing our best to protect your privacy and security. In certain areas of our websites, as identified on the site, Avianweb uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.
  * We also safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access, through access control procedures, network firewalls and physical security measures.
  * Further, Avianweb retains your personal information only as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes identified above or as required by law.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

  * Avianweb may at any time, without notice to you and in its sole discretion, amend this policy from time to time. Please review this policy periodically. Your continued use of the Avianweb website after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof.

### Questions or Suggestions

  * If you have questions or suggestions about this privacy policy, or your own personal information, please e-mail us at [sf@avianw[email protected]  
](http://www.cloudflare.com/email-protection#0c7f6a4c6d7a656d627b696e226f6361).

Revised: August 2015
